(Leonard:)I don't know what to do.
(Leonard:)The paper's terrible.
But if I tell her, she'll know that I read it...
(Leonard:)...and she'll get really mad.
(Sheldon:)I was beating him so bad
he doesn't wanna be friends anymore.
(Sheldon:)Why does everyone love me
except Stephen Hawking?
(Leonard:)Is it possible we're having
two different conversations?
(Sheldon:)How would I know?
I'm not listening to you.
(Leonard:)Hang on.
(Leonard:)Okay. Here's what we're gonna do.
Chess clock.
(Leonard:)We each get five minutes
to talk about our problems.
(Leonard:)We'll take turns.
Each turn will consist of a statement...
(Leonard:)...and a helpful response from the friend.
(Leonard:)Begin.
(Sheldon:)I humiliated Stephen Hawking
in a game of "Words With Friends."
(Sheldon:)He stopped playing.
And now we're not friends anymore.
(Leonard:)He's probably busy.
You're worried about nothing.
(Leonard:)Give it a couple more days.
I'm sure he'll play...
(Leonard:)...and you'll see that everything's fine.
(Leonard:)My turn. I can't let Penny
hand in a bad paper...
(Leonard:)...but how do I tell her it's bad
without letting her know that I read it?
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Beats me. Now...